You won't get it Now put down the phone and
see my demand is very simple
I seriously feel there is lack of
representation of helmets Now you tell me whether
safety should get importance or
not No no tell me it should get importance friend
when you have an accident I
tackle concrete stones everything I
take it head on they say na
I'll take a bullet for you friend I am
that
friend what
happened have you made an
emoji of lose too No no there is
nothing wrong in this but friend should helmet
get importance or
not I am laughing a lot Oh didi next time
when you ride a scooter don't wear a helmet keep
this pizza box on your head like this
What do you think I have anger issues
excuse me I am that friend who
reminds everyone to ride two wheelers
with safety When Sharma uncle's Riya starts
riding a scooter then I become that
expression of care now friend if you people
forget me then how will it work when
your boyfriend  If you are going on a
bike trip to Ladakh with your cow friends, then along with that
heart-shaped Dhadak emoji, add a helmet
emoji as well. So friend, make me an
emoji too and sign this petition to
[Music]
Unicorn